

SHREYA MALVIYA

Senior Software Developer

E: contactshreyamalviyaa@gmail.com | 7681953903 | **A:** Gurgaon, Haryana 122018 | **WWW:** <u>Bold Profile</u> | **LinkedIn:** www.linkedin.com/in/Shreya-Malviya-Dev

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Ambitious Java Developer versed in following established procedures and working under little or no supervision. Offering technical expertise in programming analysis, application analysis and design. Excellent team player with in-depth knowledge of development tools and languages.

WORK HISTORY

Twinline Business Solutions Pvt. Ltd. - Java Developer

Gurgaon, Haryana 07/2022 - Current

- Led API development, delivering scalable, secure, and optimized services
- Integrated UPI & UPI Mandate, enhancing MFIs payment processing and compliance.
- Built high-performance Java/Spring Boot/Hibernate applications.
- Enforced code quality, performing reviews and JUnit-based testing.
- Automated document workflows using docx4j, reducing manual effort
- Practiced Agile methodologies, collaborating across teams for full-stack delivery.
- Provided technical leadership & mentorship, solving complex challenges.

Twinline Business Solutions Pvt Ltd. - Java Developer Intern

Gurugram, Haryana 07/2021 - 06/2022

- Integrated user-facing elements developed by a front-end developer.
- Collaborated with programming analysts, designers and testers to identify needed features and edits.
- Integrated 5 data sources and databases into one system.
- Debugged and corrected computer programming errors with advisory from master developer.
- Enhanced application performance by optimizing Java code and implementing efficient algorithms.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Java, Lambdas and Streams Spring Boot, Spring Boot Microservices Docx4j, Dynamic Document Creation Maven, Gradle AWS (EC2, S3) JUnit, Mockito Hibernate ORM, JPA Thread Synchronization, Multithreading and Concurrency UPI Intent Creation and QR Code Generation API design and development SOAP and Restful Web Services HTML, CSS, JavaScript

EDUCATION

Punjab Technical University

Mohali,Punjab 01/2019 - 01/2022

Bachelor of Computer Applications

Guru Nanak Model Sr. Sec. School Ludhiana,Punjab 01/2019

Higher Secondary CertificateCBSE